Kelber, Harry Papers 6371
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harry Kelber Papers
1958-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kelber, Harry
6371
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers.
8399863
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 20, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arrangement
Series I: Correspondence
Series II: Subject Files
Kelber, Harry
8399863
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Morton Bahr Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Richard Besinger Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Aaron Coia Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Robert Pleasure Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - John Sweeney Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Richard Trumka Correspondence, 1998-2002 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Series II: Subject Files
  - AFL-CIO Biographies (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO Convention, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - AFL-CIO Executive Council, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Diary of My Trip to the Chinese People's Republic, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dr. Harry Kelber Endowment in Labor Studies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - From Harry Kelber's Website (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Kelber Campaign, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Labor College, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Labor College, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Labor College, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Labor Educator, 1978-2012 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Labor-Liberal Articles, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Labor-Liberal Arts Student Association, 1968-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Labor Strategies for Today and Tomorrow (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Leadership Institute, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Leadership Institute, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - A Plea for Sanity: Must We Perish?, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Social Security for Physicians (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Speech Course (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Testimony on Automation (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Time to Organize (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Union Printers and Controlled Automation, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cartoons (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Pamphlets, 1958-1999 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: Recessions and How to Prevent Them, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Scope and Contents
      Author: Harry Kelber; Fred Wright
      Format: Publication
      Language: English.
    - Item 2: Recessions and How To Prevent Them, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Notes: Copy 2.
    - Item 3: Recessions and How To Prevent Them, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Notes: Copy 3.
    - Item 4: Labor College Supplement to the Empire State College Student Hanbook, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Center for Labor Studies
    - Item 5: The Making of Ideal Union Members, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Harry Kelber; Ed Murawinske
    - Item 6: The Making of Ideal Union Members, 1998; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Harry Kelber; Ed Murawinski
    - Item 7: A Vision for New York Labor: Sensible, Practical Proposals To Revitalize the Union Movement, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Harry Kelber
    - Item 8: A Vision For New York Labor: Sensible, Practical Proposals to Revitalize the Union Movement, 1990; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 9: Security for Members and Their Families, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Author: Local 140 Security Fund
    - Item 10: The 'Palace Revolution' That Changed the AFL-CIO, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Item 11: The 'Palace Revolution' That Changed the AFL-CIO, 1999; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)